<resources>
  <string name="app_name">Scavengr Client</string>
  <string name="login_failure">Unable to sign in with provided credentials.</string>
  <string name="sign_out">Sign out</string>

  <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
  <string name="default_description">Default description</string>
  <string name="find_a_hunt">Find a hunt</string>
  <string name="new_hunt_button">New Hunt</string>
  <string name="next_button">Next</string>
  <string name="back_button">Back</string>
  <string name="join_hunt">JOIN THE HUNT!</string>
  <string name="find_a_hunt_prompt">Great! Now find a hunt you want to join! If you are an organizer you can create one!</string>
  <string name="camera_permission_denied">Sorry, you can\'t use the camera without granting permission</string>
  <string name="qr_dependencies_downloading">QR Detector dependencies have not finished downloading yet.  Please check your network connection and try again.</string>
  <string name="sagan_ipsum">Dispassionate extraterrestrial observer made in the interiors of collapsing stars network of wormholes quasar light years descended from astronomers? Stirred by starlight invent the universe white dwarf globular star cluster take root and flourish.</string>
  <string name="restart_camera">Camera failed.  Restarting</string>
  <string name="permission_camera_rationale">Access to the camera is needed for QR detection.</string>
  <string name="ok">OK</string>
  <string name="hide_clue">Hide clue</string>
  <string name="show_clue">Show clue</string>
  <string name="clue_content">Clue Content</string>
  <string name="clue_number">Clue #</string>
  <string name="google_account_problem">There was a problem with your Google account</string>
  <string name="welcome_hunter">Welcome hunter! What is your name?</string>
  <string name="username">Username</string>
  <string name="are_you_an_organizer">Are you an Organizer?</string>
  <string name="register">REGISTER</string>
  <string name="sagan_ipsum_two">Euclid corpus callosum a billion trillion shores of the cosmic ocean Rig Veda the ash of stellar alchemy. A still more glorious dawn awaits courage of our questions a very small stage in a vast cosmic arena rich in heavy atoms a very small stage in a vast cosmic arena rich in heavy atoms. Are creatures of the cosmos another world dream of the mind\'s eye concept of the number one the carbon in our apple pies the only home we\'ve ever known and billions upon billions upon billions upon billions upon billions upon billions upon billions.</string>

</resources>
